chrometechny.com 2015-11-24

# Privacy Policy - ChromeTechny.inChromeTechny.in

The Privacy Policy is a source for site users to understand what exactly we use on ChromeTechny.Com. Privacy of our users at ChromeTechny is extremely important to us.  ChromeTechny.com uses, collects. maintains and discloses all the information gathered from the users. This privacy is strictly applied in the entire website, to all the categories and all the services provided at ChromeTechny.Com.

## Information That May be gathered:

We may collect personal identification information from readers in different ways, which includes, Newsletter subscription, Filling out a form such as commenting, participating in conversation, services, resources that we use on ChromeTechny.

We may ask you to provide us with  that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your name, email address, postal address and phone number

While using our Site Readers may need to use certain personally identifiable information appropriate such as name, email address, phone number while participating in any conversation or content creation, **but is not limited to**. Users may, however, visit our website anonymously.  Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Information Collection And Use**

While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your name, email address, postal address and phone number (“Personal Information”).

**Log Data**

Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

**Cookies**

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive.

Like many sites, we use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Links To Other Sites**

Our Site may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

ChromeTechny.Com has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party sites or services.

**Changes To This Privacy Policy**

ChromeTechny.CoM may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site with the exact date mentioned when the changes took place. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this website, you signify your full acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
